Now that we've seen some of the operations on self type, in this video we're going to
现在我们已经看到了对Self类型的一些操作，在这个视频中，我们将
talk about where self type can be used in Cool. The parser checks if self type
谈论一下在Cool中可以使用Self类型的地方。解析器检查自身类型
appears only where types are permitted, but that's in fact a little bit too
仅在允许类型的地方出现，但这实际上也有一点
permissive. There are places where some other types can appear but self type
很宽容。有些地方可以显示除自身类型之外的其他类型
cannot, and so the purpose of this particular video is to go over the various
不能，所以这个视频的目的是复习各种
rules for the usage of self type. So let's begin with, a very simple rule. So, self
SELF类型的用法规则。让我们从一条非常简单的规则开始。所以，赛尔夫
type is not a class name so it can't appear in a class definition, can neither
类型不是类名，因此它不能出现在类定义中，也不能
be the name of the class nor the class that is inherited from. In attribute
既不是继承自的类的名称，也不是继承自的类的名称。入站属性
declarations the type of attribute in this case we have an attribute x and is
声明属性的类型在本例中，我们有一个属性x，并且是
declared to have type t, it is okay for t to be self type so it's fine to have
声明为类型t，t可以为自身类型，所以具有
attributes that are declared to be the self type of the class. Similarly, it's
声明为类的自身类型的属性。同样，它也是
fine to have local let down variables that have type self type. And it's fine to
拥有类型为self类型的局部RESHOW变量是很好的。而且这是很好的
allocate a new object of type self type. And what this actually does is that it
分配类型为Self类型的新对象。而这实际上做的是它
allocates an object that has the same dynamic type as the self object. So,
分配与Self对象具有相同动态类型的对象。所以,
whatever the type of the self object happens to be, which is not necessarily
不管Self对象的类型是什么，这不一定是
the type of the enclosing class at run time, the u t operation will create a new
运行时封闭类的类型，则u t操作将创建一个新的
object of that dynamic type. The type named in aesthetic dispatch cannot be self
该动态类型的。美学调度中命名的类型不能为自身
type, again because it has to be an actual class name. Finally let's consider method
类型，同样因为它必须是实际的类名。最后，让我们考虑一下方法
definitions. So, here's a very simple method definition. It has one formal
定义。所以，这里有一个非常简单的方法定义。它有一个正式的
parameter X of type T and the method returns something of type T prime. And it
类型为T的参数X，该方法返回类型为T的素数。而且它
turns out that only T prime, only the return type can be of type self-type. No
原来只有T素数，只有返回类型可以是SELF类型。不是的
argument type can be of type self-type. And to see why let's, I can show it
参数类型可以是自类型。想知道为什么，我可以展示给大家看
actually two different ways. Why, why this has to be the case. And we'll do both
实际上有两种不同的方式。为什么，为什么一定要这样。我们两个都要做
because this is actually important. So, let's think about a dispatch to this a
因为这实际上很重要。那么，让我们想一想派往这里的消息
method, so let's say we have some expression e, and we call method m, and we
方法，所以假设我们有一些表达式e，我们调用方法m，我们
have some argument e prime. And now, let's say the argument e prime As the
有一些论点e素数。现在，让我们把论点e‘作为
type t zero. So if you recall the rule for method calls, t zero is gonna have to be a
键入t0。所以如果你回想一下方法调用的规则，t0必须是一个
sub type of the type of the fall parameter. We're gonna be passing this in,
Fall参数类型的子类型。我们会把这个交给你，
so whatever type x is declared to have here has to be a super type of the type of
因此，这里声明的任何类型x都必须是
the actual argument. So that means that t zero is going to have to be a sub type of,
真正的论据。所以这意味着t0将会是一个子类型，
now let's assume that the argument can be of type self type. Some view that t zero
现在让我们假设参数可以是self类型。一些人认为测试为零
has to be a subtype of self type this is in some class c wherever this is defined,
必须是SELF类型的子类型，它在某个类C中，无论它是在哪里定义的，
and remember that we said This was always false that you couldn't have self type on
记住，我们说过这总是假的，你不能自己打字
the right hand side and a regular type on the left hand side. Because that would
右手边的，左手边的普通字体。因为那样会
lead to problems that would, that we would never be able to prove that in general for
导致的问题，我们将永远不能证明这一点，一般情况下
a, that, that a type is actually a sub type of self type because self type can
A，就是说，一个类型实际上是自我类型的一个子类型，因为自我类型可以
vary over all the sub types of the class C. So that's one way to see that we can't
在类C的所有子类型上有所不同，所以这是我们看不到的一种方式
allow method parameters, to be typed self type, but it's also helpful to just think
允许将方法参数类型化为自身类型，但仅考虑这一点也很有帮助
about executing the code or some example code and see what can go wrong. So here's
关于执行代码或一些示例代码，并查看可能出错的地方。所以这里是
an example. And let me just walk you through what happens if we allow a
举个例子。让我给你们讲讲如果我们允许
parameter to have type self type in this example. So there are two class
在此示例中，参数的类型为Self类型。所以有两个班级
definitions. Class A has a method comp for comparison, and it takes one argument of
定义。类A有一个用于比较的方法comp，它的一个参数是
type self-type. And it returns a bull. So the idea here is that the comparison
键入self-type。它会返回一头公牛。所以这里的想法是比较
operation probably compares the, this parameter with the argument and returns
操作可能会将，this参数与实参进行比较，并返回
true or false. Then, there's a second class B, and B is a sub-type of A, it
对或错。然后，还有第二个B类，B是A的一个子类型，它
inherits from A. And it has one new field B little b here of type int. And now the
继承自A，这里有一个int类型的新字段。而现在
comparison function in class B is overridden has the same signature as the
类B中的比较函数被重写，其签名与
comparison function or the comp function in class A. But, the, the method body here
类A中的比较函数或Comp函数。但是，这里的方法体
accesses the field B. And now let's take a look at what happens with a piece of code
访问字段B。现在让我们看看一段代码会发生什么情况
that uses these two classes. So, here X is going to be declared to be of type A. But
使用这两个类的。这里，X将被声明为类型A，但是
we're going to assign it something of type B. And here we're notice that there's a
我们将它指定为B类型，这里我们注意到有一个
gap between the static type, which will be A, and the dynamic type, which will be B.
静电类型(将为A)和动态类型(将为B)之间的差距。
And that's actually key to the problem. And now, we Invoke the cup method on X and
这实际上是问题的关键。现在，我们调用X和X上的Cup方法
we pass it a new A object. And so what happens, well this type checks just fine
我们给它传递一个新的A对象。那么会发生什么呢，嗯，这种类型的检查很好
because X is in class A. X is of type A and this argument is also of type A. So if
因为X在A类中。X是A类型的，这个参数也是A类型的。所以如果
self-type if having an argument type self-type is ever going to work it has to
Self类型如果有一个参数类型，那么Self类型永远不会起作用，它必须
work for this example where the two static types of the, of the dispatched of this
工作在此示例中，这两种静电类型的、已调度的
parameter and the former parameter are exactly the same. So that clearly has to
参数和前一个参数完全相同。所以这显然是必须的
be allowed if we allow self type as the type of the argument. And now let's think
如果我们允许Self类型作为参数的类型，则允许。现在让我们想想
about what happens when it actually executes Is going to invoke the comp
关于它实际执行时发生的事情将调用comp
method in the b class okay, Because X is of dynamic type B. And then it's going to
方法，因为X是动态类型B，然后它将
take the arguments and it's going to access its B field. But the argument is of
接受参数，它将访问它的B字段。但论点是
dynamic type A and it has no B field. And so, this is actually going to cause a
动态类型A，并且没有B字段。因此，这实际上会导致
runtime crash. So, and just to go over that one more time, Just to make sure that
运行时崩溃。所以，我再重复一遍，只是为了确保
it is clear. Here X has type A ut dynamic type B. The argument has static type A and
很明显。此处X的类型为A，但动态类型为B。参数的类型为静电类型A，并且
dynamic type A and when this method gets invoked the argument That which is of
动态类型A，并且当调用此方法时，
dynamic type A, does not have the operations, all the fields and methods, of
动态类型A没有的操作、所有字段和方法
the class B And results in a run time, undefined behavior at run time.
类B和导致运行时未定义的运行时行为。